<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cardiff Math Code Club</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://CardiffMathematicsCodeClub.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://CardiffMathematicsCodeClub.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A first blog post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The end of a busy term has given me a bit of time to add a blog to this site.
I’ll keep this post fairly short but will nonetheless use it to reflect on a great first 11 weeks of code club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;student-engagement&quot;&gt;Student engagement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been really nice to see students engage with Code club and participate in various ways.
One such ‘way’ has been the design/maintenance of this website.
I look forward to seeing this continue and am very grateful to the students who made this a really fun and awesome time (thanks).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a picture of the last Code club of term during which we tested out Ambrose’s work analysing Monopoly:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/static/images/monopoly.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a picture of one of the moments during which a group of students and I were trying to figure out the best database to use for a neat project that we will hopefully finish next term:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/static/images/mongodb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks&quot;&gt;Thanks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big thank you to Jason who has given up a lot of his time to help/encourage students working on various projects.
Jason does not have much free time at all and he has very selflessly always been one of the last to leave code club if there was ever a student wanting a hand with anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;neat-things-to-come&quot;&gt;Neat things to come&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s hopefully going to be a neat couple of additions to the Code club room in the new semester which should help students wanting to learn new skills…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the subject of next term, it’ll be interesting to see how Code club evolves with the various company projects that will be part of the Spring semester of my Computing for Mathematics module.
I hope it’ll be busy :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://CardiffMathematicsCodeClub.github.io/website/2014/12/14/A-first-blog-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://CardiffMathematicsCodeClub.github.io/website/2014/12/14/A-first-blog-post.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
